sharingsmiles.co 2019-12-25

# sharingsmiles.co - Privacy Policy

_Last updated:_ July 2019

Welcome to Sharingsmiles’s internet website, at [sharingsmiles.co](https://sharingsmiles.co/) (the **“Site”** ). The Site and its owners ( **“Us** **“** or “ **We** “) are committed to your right to privacy. This privacy policy applies to information collected via the Site and/or the services available through the Site or otherwise provided by Us (the “ **Services** ”).

In this Privacy Policy:

The terms “ **User** ” or “ **you** ” mean any user of the Site and/or Services.

The term “ **Content”** means any data, information, news, text, photographs, graphics, video and audio links, clips and profiles uploaded to the Site by the User.We value your trust, and therefore strive to present you this policy in clear, plain language, so you can quickly find answers to the questions that interest you. If you use/visit the Site or otherwise choose to register or submit information to the Site and Services, you agree to the use of any data collected or uploaded in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Please note, that the Services may contain links to other websites maintained by third parties, which may not be governed by this Privacy Policy. Terms not defined herein shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of User

**1\. What Information we collect?**

**Personal information**

You may use our Service without providing any information which is personally identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, or may be of private nature (“Personal Information”). However, you may voluntarily provide us with Personal Information.

The Personal Information you may voluntarily provide includes your email-address, when you decide to register to our newsletter or receive from us promotional material, as disclosed below.

You may also voluntarily provide us with social network identifier or your profile details on any approved platform (e.g. Facebook or Twitter); you hereby warrant that we may retrieve and use information accessible or stored in such service related to you or your contacts. We will retrieve such information in accordance with the security restrictions and applicable permissions of the respected platform. We do not store or process password or security related information.

**Non-personal information**

We collect certain information pertaining to a user, which may be made available or gathered via the user’s use of the Service (“Non-personal Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the user from which the Non-personal Information was collected. Non-personal Information which is being collected consists of technical information transmitted by your device and aggregated usage information, and contains certain software and hardware information about your device, the referring page that linked you to our Service, including the type of browser and operating system your device uses, operator, language preference, access time, and the domain name of the website from which you linked or registered to the Service.

**2\. How we may collect your information** **?**

  * We collect information submitted directly by you, or information transmitted automatically from your device using various standard technologies, such as cookies, digital identifiers, log files, web beacons or other similar technologies.
  * Our Service may automatically send cookies to your system. The Company may store information which correlates with those cookies, and designed to improve and optimize the Service.
  * You may block and remove our cookies through your browser and operating system, but this may impair and hinder the Service functionality and availability.
  * The Company may use logs and cookie information to improve quality and design of the Service, including without limitation, saving you the trouble of re-entering data, and quarries, personalize and customize the Service, track your use of the Service and generate statistics regarding the Service.

**What is a “cookie”?**

When you use our Service we may assign your device with a log file or a cookie (session or persistent). A “cookie” is a small piece of information that a website assign to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and making the interaction between you and the Service quicker and easier. Cookies are also used to help ensure that the advertisements you see are relevant to you and your interests. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You may remove our cookies by following the instructions of your browser preferences; however, if you choose to disable cookies, some features of our Service may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited.

**What are we using it for?**

We may use cookies, log files, web beacons and other technologies to collect Non-Personal Information with respect to your activity on our Service and track your use of our Service, your type of browser, pages you visited, the time and date of your visits or the links you click on.

We may also allow third parties, e.g. service providers (i.e. third parties that perform services on our behalf; e.g. customer service, marketing assistance, analytics, ad tracking, service functionality and support, surveys, etc.), ad networks and advertising companies, to display advertisements on our Service. These parties may also use the technologies stated above to collect information about our users. We do not provide any Personal Information to third parties, unless indicated otherwise in our Privacy Policy.

You can learn more about cookies at the following third-party websites:

AllAboutCookies: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

Network Advertising Initiative: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**3\. How we use the information we collect** **?**

  * To respond to your inquiries, support request, feedbacks or questions, and update you with information pertaining to your request, and respond to claims that any content available through the Service violates the rights of third-parties;
  * To enhance and personalize our promotions offers and customize the advertising content we display;
  * To communicate with you (via email, etc.);
  * To resolve disputes and enforce our policies, including investigation of potential violations thereof, or in accordance with any applicable law or regulation, or for the purpose of law enforcement;
  * To perform research, technical diagnostics, analytics or statistical purposes;
  * To provide you with the most relevant additional services and offers.
  * To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

**4\. With whom we share the information, and for what purpose** **?**

**Service Providers**

We share your information with our affiliated companies and our third party professional service providers, who are allowed to use the information only for the purposes of providing the Service to you, or with our affiliated companies and business partners for performing services for us (e.g. customer service, conducting promotions, marketing assistance, technical support, analytics, etc.).

If you provided us with your email-address, we may transfer it to our marketing affiliates or our other subsidiaries to provide you with recent news, interesting updates and marketing offers or promotions.

The information will be disclosed only to the extent required to perform the purposes as stipulated herein.

You hereby warrant and consent that your Personal Information may be transmitted, used or stored with our authorized third parties, for the purposes disclosed herein, which are located across the world.

**Other Disclosures**

We may share your information, including Personal Information, in the event that we are required by law enforcement or other governmental agency; in response to a subpoena, warrant or an investigative demand, or a court order, or with respect to any legal process; in order to enforce intellectual property rights or to exercise other legal rights; to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims; if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing, safety of person or property, violation of our policies, to enforce our policies or as otherwise required in order to comply with the applicable laws and regulations. In such circumstances, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

**Affiliates and corporate transaction**

We may share Information, with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively “affiliated companies”). We may share information in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale).

In the event of the above, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Aggregated Information**

Non-Personal Information, aggregated information or Personal Information in non-human readable form (de-identified) may be shared with third parties (including ad networks, advertising companies and service providers) in any of the above circumstances, as well as for the purpose of developing or delivering tailored or targeted advertising (whether via our Service, or websites or applications of third parties), or for the purpose of improving our Service, conducting business analysis or other business purposes. This information may be combined with information we collect from other sources, to the extent that the information remains Non-Personal Information.

**Third party collection of information**

Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties via our Service (whether our website or application; e.g. by clicking on a link to any other website or location) or via other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We prompt you to review the privacy policies of those sites before providing your Personal Information to them.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Publisher Common ID: Opt-Out  

**5\. For how long we retain the information** **we collect?**

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion.

To remove your email address please contact us at [info@sharingsmiles.co](mailto:info@sharingsmiles.co)

Please note that unless you instruct us otherwise we retain the information we collect (including your Personal Information) for as long as needed to provide the Service and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

**6\. Direct Marketing**

If you provided us with your email address, we may use it from time to time in connection with promotional activities or bonus programs, and share it with our marketing partners or use it ourselves for the purpose of providing you recent news, interesting updates and marketing offers or promotions. As we are committed to your right to privacy, we provide you with simple tools to decline receiving email offers from us or from our affiliates and partners – you may, at any time, choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email communication that we will send you.

Please note that even if you have unsubscribed from receiving promotional emails from us, we may send you other types of important e-mail communications without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. These may include customer service announcements, administrative notices and surveys.

Also, please note that changing your information in your registration account, or opting out of receiving promotional email communications from us will affect only future communications from us. If we already provided your information to a third party (such as a marketing affiliate) before you changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change your preferences directly with that third party as well.

**7\. Children Information**

Our Service is not intended for minors, in particular children under the age of 13, and we will not knowingly collect personal information from children. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13, we will remove their information from our files. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that children are not using the Service.

**8\. Assignment**

If We elect, in its reasonable discretion, to transfer ownership or control of the Site or Services to a third party, whether or not in the context of an acquisition, merger, or reorganization, you consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information by Us to that third party, provided that all use of your information by that third party remains subject to the terms of this Policy.

**9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. You are encouraged to check and revisit this page as often as you wish to update yourself with any changes. If you have any questions regarding this policy or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to: info@sharingsmiles.co.

**10\. Securing Information and Data**

We implement in the Site advanced data security systems. However, these systems can not fully ensure a risk free environment and to completely prevent infiltration by unwelcome parties. Therefore, We will not commit that our Services are completely resistant from an unauthorized party invasion.

**11\. Right to Access Data**

According to the Protection of Privacy Law, 1981 (the “ **Law** “), any person is entitled to review any information being gathered with regards to that person in any database. If you reviewed the information or data and found them to be incomplete or incorrect, you are entitled to contact us in order to make the relevant changes or to completely delete the information, through the following contact details:

Email: info@sharingsmiles.co

In addition, if the information in the database is made use of to personally contact you, you may, by law, demand in writing to erase this information from the database.
